let's say you have some JavaScript code that lives in a single file you can turn
假设您有一些 JavaScript 代码存在于单个文件中，您可以
this code into a module by exporting it this allows other files to use an import
通过将其导出将此代码转换为模块，这允许其他文件使用
statement to import this file as a dependency so a module is nothing more
import 语句将此文件作为依赖项导入，因此模块只不过是
than a file that exports its own code this allows developers to organize code
一个文件 导出自己的代码这允许开发人员
within their own projects or share code with the world through package managers
在自己的项目中组织代码或通过
like NPM in modern front-end development it's most common to use es modules which
现代前端开发中的 NPM 等包管理器与世界共享代码最常见的是使用 es 模块，该模块
became an official language feature in 2015 the syntax is also supported in
在 2015 年成为官方语言功能语法也是 在
note 13 but traditionally the way to do this a node is with required Jas it's a
注释 13 中支持，但传统上执行此操作的方法是使用 required Jas 节点，这是一个
similar idea but instead we use this require function to import a module
类似的想法，但我们使用此require 函数来导入模块
require is more common now but the future is es modules a module can export
require 现在更常见，但未来是 es modules 模块可以导出
its code in a variety of ways and this will affect the way the consumer imports
其代码 多种方式，这将影响消费者导入
it a module can export a single default value multiple values or both if a
它的方式模块可以导出单个默认值多个值或两者如果
module provides a default export it means the consumer can call import name
模块提供默认导出它意味着 ns 消费者可以
from path the importing file can choose whatever name it wants but a module also
从路径中调用导入名称 导入文件可以选择它想要的任何名称，但是模块
has the option to expose multiple exports from a single file you can
还可以选择从单个文件公开多个导出，您可以
export them one by one or all together as a single export list on the other
将它们一个一个导出或一起导出为单个导出列表
side the importer will use the exact name used in the module however it is
另一方面，导入器将使用模块中使用的确切名称，但是
possible to rename an import using the as keyword a huge benefit of named
可以使用 as 关键字重命名导入命名导出的一个巨大好处
exports is that they make the module tree shakable that means the consumer
是它们使模块树可摇动，这意味着使用者
only imports the code they actually need resulting in smaller bundle sizes and
只导入他们实际需要的代码导致更小的包大小和
better performance you can also combine the best of both worlds to give you a
更好的性能你还可以结合两全其美，为你提供一个
hybrid syntax that looks like this it helps to have a cheat sheet my personal
看起来像这样的混合语法它有助于有一个备忘单我个人
favorite is the one from Samantha Ming if you don't already follow her awesome
最喜欢的是来自 Samantha Ming如果你还没有遵循 她
post on Twitter you definitely should be this has been yes modules and 100
在 Twitter 上的精彩帖子你绝对应该是这个模块和 100
seconds thanks for watching and I will see you in the next one
秒感谢观看，我会在下一个看到你